The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Giant Demon Clan
Ancestor,
what's wrong with you ?
I will take your body !
That demon child destroyed my body
and injured my Origin Soul.
If I hadn't lured him to the extreme north
to use the ancient restriction that is there,
I likely wouldn't have escaped this calamity.
Not only did I fail to capture Wang Lin
but I was also severely injured.
The only thing I obtained was this celestial sword.
Sword Spirit,
come out !
My lord, have mercy.
Please don't kill me.
I was forced by that person named Wang.
I also hate him to the bones...
You are certainly a strange Sword Spirit.
Most are very determined and loyal.
Your grandpa Xu...
How could those servant Sword Spirits compare to me ?
A wise man knows whom he should follow...
This sword is no ordinary object.
A Sword Spirit that possesses intelligence
is really rare.
It would be a pity
to erase it.
While my Origin Soul is merging with this body,
I will seal it
and see what happens.
Since you surrendered on your own...
From now on,
you shall be this old man's Sword Spirit.
Don't try to escape.
My lord, don't worry.
Xu Liguo has always been loyal.
I wouldn’t dare to betray you !
If I break this oath
let 10 000 demons pierce my heart !
You'll accompany me in seclusion.
When my Origin Soul is 50% merged with this body,
we will settle the score with Wang Lin !
Master !
When will you come to save me !?
They say the Soul Refining Sect is the most mysterious sect of Pilu.
They never actively recruit disciples,
they only take those willing to bite the bait.
As long as you pay the spirit stones on the opening day
you will get a cave for cultivation.
A sect protection formation...
Who dares trespass into our Soul Refining Sect !?
Hong Maozi\NSoul Refining Sect's outer sect Elder\NEarly stage Core Formation
Greetings Senior,
Junior apologizes for intruding.
I've come to join the Soul Refining Sect.
Which sect are you from ?
Disciple is a rogue cultivator.
Reaching Foundation Establishment as a rogue isn't easy...
But our outer disciple recruitment period ended long ago.
Come back in a few years.
Senior, please wait !
This is a flying sword that Junior found a few years ago.
I've been saving it.
Please Senior, accept it.
How does this kid have such an artifact ?
Where did you find this ?
Many years ago, I helped a Core Formation cultivator.
I protected him while he recovered from an injury.
After recovering, he gifted me this sword.
But disciple's cultivation is too low
to use it.
Okay,
I can see that you worked hard,
so I'll make an exception.
Follow me closely.
There are many restrictions in the sect.
If you enter one of them,
I won't save you.
Thank you Senior !
As the jade slip said,
the spiritual energy is very dense here.
Using so much spiritual energy
for thousands of outer disciples
is truly extravagant.
It's exactly what I need.
Brother Chang.
Brother Chang !
Chang Dawei\NSoul Refining Sect's outer sect Elder\NEarly stage Core Formation
I'm here,
what are you shouting for ?
This is a junior I met on the way.
Brother Chang, how about you take him as an outer disciple ?
Since Hong Maozi asked personally,
how could I refuse ?
I leave him to you then.
This time
I gathered 100 vengeful souls.
I'll add them to my Soul Flag and make one a primary soul.
Once I'm done,
I'll come to drink with you.
Hong Maozi never acts without benefit,
what did you give him ?
A sword
that a Senior gave me.
Since that's the case,
cave 1090 shall be yours.
One mid quality spirit stone per year.
This cave has little spiritual energy,
its vein looks depleted.
Senior,
may I switch to a better cave ?
Cultivators mustn't be greedy.
Your foundation
is unstable.
If you keep this up, you will never reach Core Formation.
May Junior ask one more thing ?
What's this Soul Flag Hong Maozi mentioned ?
Do you know
that our sect has only 100 inner disciples ?
Yet it still can rival other sects of the country of Pilu.
That's because of Soul Flags.
What are they ?
The Soul Flags
are our sect's unique artifacts.
Their secrets are only for inner disciples.
Back then,
I fought my way into the inner sect.
But since I stayed too long at early Core Formation,
I lost my status
and became an outer sect elder.
Could Senior share some insights ?
You're not qualified yet.
Outer disciples compete every 3 years.
A single one gets to enter the inner sect.
If you want to know,
try yourself.
Junior apologizes.
What's your name ?
Disciple's name is Qian Mu.
Enough,
follow me.
I looked everywhere
but couldn't find a trace of his aura.
What happened to him ?
Outer disciples cave 803\NSoul Refining Sect
The lower the cave number,
the more spiritual energy it has.
For Hong Maozi's sake,
I gave you a Spirit Vein location.
Thank you Senior,
Junior will repay you.
Tens of thousands of outer disciples...
But only one can enter the inner sect.
Yet the sect spends vast resources on outers...
What's their true purpose ?
Surely not just helping disciples cultivate.
A Spirit Vein ?
Crystal Kun Stone
So they use a Crystal Kun Stone to gather energy
and a spirit gathering formation to contain it.
A clever way to make a false Spirit Vein.
But if I break the restriction
and use the Crystal Kun Stone directly,
I should be able to reach Late stage Foundation Establishment.
With my current cultivation,
breaking the restriction
will be difficult.
But it's worth trying.
Break !
Foundation Establishment
Peak Late stage
This cave's spiritual energy is depleted...
I wonder
how Wan'er is doing...
Only 7 years left...
I have to speed up.
I will find a true Spirit Vein
to fully break the Tea Domain
and sealing mark.
Outer disciples cave 743\NSoul Refining Sect
This cave
must be the closest to the true Spirit Vein.
But it's occupied...
Qian Mu
Senior
Peak Late stage Foundation Establishment !
He has mediocre talent
but in just 3 months
he leaped from Early to Peak Late stage Foundation Establishment.
He either has a heaven defying artifact
or his cultivation method is very profound !
I'm afraid the next time we meet,
I'll have to call you fellow cultivator.
Since my Origin Soul collapsed,
I can't conceal my cultivation.
Since this Core Formation cultivator noticed,
he's going to be troublesome to deal with...
This land is blessed,
Junior cultivated day and night
and got lucky in breakthroughs.
If you reach Core Formation,
you will have a good chance to win
the sect competition in 3 months.
If you enter the inner sect,
remember to visit me sometimes.
By the way,
let me warn you.
The sect competition only has one rule:
winner takes all.
As long as you win,
life or death doesn't matter.
Thank you Senior for the advice.
If I can learn Qian Mu's cultivation method,
I may be able to re-enter the inner sect !
Weird...
Why did he leave the door open ?
He's just a mere Foundation Establishment,
killing him will be easy.
So you have come.
Qian Mu,
hand over your cultivation secrets !
And if I refuse ?
You have no choice !
The sect doesn't care
about the lives of outer disciples.
If you hand it over,
I will spare you.
Otherwise...
You really have good artifacts !
But they'll all be mine today !
What is this thing !?
You can't kill me,
I'm an outer sect elder !
The sect doesn't care
about the lives of outer disciples.
There's no way
you're just at Foundation Establishment...
Who exactly are you !?
You're not worthy
to know who I am.
Who ?
Sen...
Senior !
Seal !
Spirit Vein mine\NSoul Refining Sect
A Spirit Vein mine...
The spiritual energy here is so dense
that it creates spirit stones naturally.
It's the perfect place
for breaking the seal.
Fall !
I'm going all out !
Again !
Break !
Early stage
Core Formation
Break !
Middle stage
Core Formation
Late stage
What happened ?
What's going on ?
The mountain exploded !
Such a powerful pressure !
Early stage\N\NNascent Soul
Middle stage
Nascent Soul
Break !
Peak Middle stage Nascent Soul
To let go of the consequences of my actions
is to ignore the law of cause and effect
like scattered ink.
As destiny falls
in exchange for this moment of tainted dreams.
It makes the mountains lose their colors,
wither and melt into rivers.
Who can deceive
the law of the heavens ?
Countless generations
have tried before me.
But how could I not catch my dreams
within my warm fingers ?
You're at my side when I'm alone
giving me the strength to fight the will of the heavens.
Fortunately, my mind was open and honest.
I'm sorry we never got to see the fireworks
in the streets.
Can I break the vortex of our destiny ?
Can I break the rules ?
To run towards you !
I will fight the law of the heavens and the law of cause and effect
to cut down this tribulation with my own hands
and break through the reincarnation cycle.
All of that for the stars in your eyes.
I wish to bend this dream for the fire in my heart.
If your soul is willing to wander,
can I still take your hands
and hold them tight ?
I will defy the heavens and prevent the stars from falling.
I will overthrow the Immortals and the Demons in my heart.
I dream of destroying
the shackles of our fate.
You're the only one that can ignore the law of cause and effect.
You're the hardest to let go of.
I want to be with you again
so I can look in your eyes.
Even for a moment, it's worth it.